Galgal Channel, GO!
WOW!
I made a mistake!
Today is a collaboration project.
Three guys from Ice Cream are here.
Please do.
Yes, nice to meet you all on the Galgal Channel.
I am Ice Cream.
I'm Rui.
I am Yuna.
I am Hinata.
Nice to meet you.
I'm going to collaborate with a new album called "Rock Steady," which will be released on September 6.
I'm going to collaborate with them.
I would like to use it as an opportunity
I would like to do the hidden dance with Rocksteady.
I've been looking forward to it.
I've been prepping.
I've seen everyone do it on various songs before.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm a little scared because there are 11 of us.
Let's start the video!
Yes, actually, the opening I just did was a fake opening.
was a fake opening.
This time, I'm going to try to surprise you with ice cream.
Congratulations!
Today's topic is...
It's a series of four surprises.
The first one is "I'm going to put on my own clothes without permission.
Who's going to participate?
Three of you.
Who's wearing who?
Louie's.
I'm Yuna-sama.
I, Hinata-chan, right?I'm Hinatachi-yan.
I wear it without permission.
And the second one is
While I was watching a dance video
While I was watching the dance video, a ghostly thing came out of the video.
The first one from last time.
I just took this picture.
I think it's quite surprising.
It's so effective that I included it again this time.
This is really good.
Then, I put a cracker, which Yohka also did.
I inserted one of the mystery crackers.
And here is the end of the project.
After that, the main project
It was a fake main event.
during the blindfold dance.
And the staff
And then the staff was gone.
Only the three of us.
I'm thinking of setting up a rock-paper-scissors dance in the next four years.
I'd like to set up a rockery in 4 years.
What do you think?
I'm looking forward to it.
And it's nice to meet you.
YouTube photo
I'm a guest.
I don't know what to say to the guests, but...
I'm a little bit, you know, the most casual clothes.
It's just the way you cut it.
I'm sorry.
I'll do my best not to be admired on my channel.
Let's start the video!
Fun!
Dressed up, dressed up, dressed up.
OK OK OKOkay, okay, okay.
You know you're wearing them.
I'm dressed!
Mmm.
Mm-hm.
Mm-mm.
No, wait. Minami's wearing my clothes, too.
You guys don't say that again.
Come on, I got someone.
But, come on, come on, siren, siren, siren.
Take a picture together.
No, if you can say it.
You don't think it's a surprise? Surprise, right?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm just saying, you're wearing it in style.
It looks better on you than it does on me.
What?
Yuna, Yuna, Yuna, Yuna.
What are you doing?
It looks good on you.
You can stop it.
I'll give you so much, I'll give you so much.
I'll give it to you.
It fits perfectly.
You look like my grandma, Kira.
I don't know... I feel like a grandma.
This place is...
It fits in. It looks cool with its original style.
When Yokachan came in, I wondered if we happened to be together.
We're the same.
But I was convinced.
It's my heart.
What? It looks good on you.What? It looks good on you.
It looks great on you.
What's this?
What? It was prepared, so I just put it on.
It was right over there.
Let's get started.
I've got a lot of work to do.
I think it looks pretty good.
It looks good on you.
The height is just right.
It looks better on you than it does on us.
I think I'll just go home.
I'll give it to you. As is.
Okay. Okay, then, let's watch the video.
Okay. Okay, here we go. Start!
We can do it here, right?
It's around here, isn't it? Here.
I think we're in trouble here.
Even in this condition.
I don't like the idea of bumping into it here.
I think we're in trouble after this.
It's bad here. It's the center.
But what happens after this is bad.
I'll never be able to take a picture.
I'll definitely hit someone with my hand.
That's right.
Even without the blindfold.
That's right. Even without the blindfold.
You've already bumped into him.
It's impossible here.
We'll definitely run into each other.
We'll just have to go with confidence.
It's just a feeling.
We'll never make it here.
Isn't this rusty?Isn't rusty from here?
Here.
It's not good.
If we get to this point already.
I know.
Someone's really close,
Taber? I don't know, maybe he's doing a "Taber"?
So I apologize.
I don't like it.
You scared me.
Ew!
Te-e-e-e-e!
Aaaaah!
Don't look at me today.
Today is that kind of day.
I'm afraid everyone will look at me.
Hey, Miki.
Surprised by me?
I look like you.
Why do I look like everyone?
You react well, don't you?
I'm surprised.
I guess that's the way it used to be.
But you had to do it because you had to beg for it.
It's cheap.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
It looks great on you.
Because, you know, everyone was so smooth to make us sit here.
Like, "It's hot.
Is that what you mean?
That's what guests are like.
We were fooled.
You must have had a lot of crashes.
Then, no.Then no.
Don't do this.
I don't need it anymore.
I made a very serious comment.
I was surprised.
Let's start the music!
Who is it?
Who?
I can't. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Around here.
On the left.
Three, two, one, yes.
How do you do that?
Where's Yuuka?
He's right here.
I'm scared.
Here I go.
Who's there?
Misaki?
Here.
I'm scared.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Sorry.
Coming through.
Where?
Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
It's over here.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Oh, my God. That's amazing.
It's the center.Center.
Oh no.
Oh no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
No, it's not.
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Where are you going?
I'm going. Here we go.
Here?
This way.
I'm coming. I'm coming.
Where?
I'm going.
Let's go.
Who's there? Who?
By the way...
I'm here.
Wait. Killer?
Let's be serious for a second.
Quiet. Quiet.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I think it's pretty perfect.
Wait. I left the sun.
One, two, three, four.
This way.
Hey! All right!
Hey!
Hey, it's okay, right?
No, wait, wait, wait, wait. I was in the hobby with Hyuga.
We're Ali's people. We'll never waver.
We, Ali, will never waver.
When we get caught unlined up with an ego-mic...
I think we should take this opportunity to change the Galgal channel to the Ice Cream channel
Ice CreamIce cream.
I thought you said there were only three.
That was fun, right?
Pretty much by myself.
I was pretty much number two to number one.
I was number one, and then I started taking pictures of this.
And on and on.
Everybody, take a picture of Ali.
Everyone took pictures.
Later on, Yoko said, "Let's be quiet from here on.
Yeah, that's why she was angry. She was so angry.
So I thought, oh, that's why it's quiet now.
I'm serious, this way.
Today, he's really excited.
Yeah, people are not going to get excited at all from now on.
But, you know, you can reach up here and nobody's gonna bump into you.
Oh, that's nice.
It's fun.
I'm so scared.
The staff said bye-bye in the middle of the second number.
Ask me.
Embarrassing.
Yeah, I know. Surprise, surprise. Everyone's leaving.
Oh, thank you.
Great success!
It was a success.
You were filming my eyes.
What's wrong?
Yuna's not even looking at me.
Turn around.
I guess it was perfect.
This is the center.
Keep it right here.
Thank you.
Why don't you do it?Why don't you do it?
It's a surprise.
Seriously?
So thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
I thought you guys gave me the best response.
Please rate, comment and subscribe!
Bye bye!
This time I am wearing D-Holic's costume!
ok